adsoftinc.biz 2013-08-20

# Adsoft

**Adsoft Privacy Statement**

**Information Collection And Use**

**Information Collection**   
AdSoft is the sole owner of the information collected on AdSoft.com. Other than via "cookies" and the analysis of server log files, we do not collect information from our users. 

**Cookies**   
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to keep track of a user's order when they move through our site. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. See http://www.cookiecentral.com/faq/ for more information. 

**Log Files**   
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Communications from the Site**

**Sharing**

**Legal Disclaimer**   
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. We do not sell any personally identifiable information to third parties. 

**Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**   
We do not share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. However, we do store aggregate data so that we provide outside sources with general traffic statistics from our website (for example, we may use aggregate information in a press release that states "traffic at AdSoft increased 40% this week.") 

**Notification of Changes**   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

**Contact Information**   
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: Postal Address: 

AdSoft  
1521 Golden Birch Place  
Chico, CA 95928 

URL: http://adsoftinc.biz/
